

To Minh Triet

JUNIOR REACTJS

17/01/2001

**** 0775509168

Ho Chi Minh city

www.linkedin.com/in/tmtriet-work

1 https://tmt-mo.github.io/Portfolio/

INTRODUCTION

I am a Junior React developer with one year of experience, specializing in ReactJS and TypeScript. Recently, I've worked on booking systems and marketplace platforms using Ant Design, NextJs and MobX. I am also skilled in creating responsive and user-friendly UIs with forms and tables, ensuring a positive UX that meets customer requirements.

EDUCATION

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2023

MAJORS IN: SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

- <u>Main subjects</u>: Computer science, OOP, Web application programming,
 Computer science for practicing engineers, Software architecture and design,
 Project management, Information system application-Database.
- Grade: 8.29 => GPA: 3.30

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR REACTJS DEVELOPER

10/2023 - 08/2024

BMD SOLUTIONS

- Proficient in React v18, Typescript, Ant Design, MomentJs, Scss, TailwindCss, and other React UI libraries including React-big-calendar and ExcelJs.
- Specialized in developing admin websites for Booking Systems (Spa, Hospital, Hotel), and marketplace platforms. Notable projects include Fclass, Vitadairy, and Joy Bookie, where I gained experience in working with tables, forms, and data display.
- Regularly utilize custom hooks for efficient data handling, along with common hooks such as useState, useRef, useMemo, useCallback, useImperativeHandle, and useEffect.
- Collaborate closely with a leader who is also responsible in Backend to brainstorm ideas and solutions for optimizing module performance and enhancing UI aesthetics.
- Participate in daily meetings with team members to review progress, discuss ongoing tasks, troubleshoot challenges, and devise solutions.
- Frequently engage with clients to gather feedback on software UI/ UX and improvements, ensuring that their needs and concerns are addressed effectively.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

10/2022 - 06/2023

VAN LANG UNIVERSITY - GRADUATE PROJECT

- Working with React v18 and Typescript, TailwindCss, Material UI, RESTful API.
- Creating custom axios requests (handle requests, expire token with interceptor).
- · Managing asynchorous actions and global states with Redux thunk.
- My role was a team leader and a Frontend developer. I lead my team (6 people) and got a pretty high grade as 8.0.
- Come up with plan and schedule suiltable date with customer to discuss what will do next, review the progress and also organizing daily meeting with team mates

INTERN REACTJS

07/2022 - 10/2022

CÔNG TY CỔ PHẦN KỶ NGUYÊN SỐ

- Using React, Redux Thunk to manage asynchronous actions.
- · Combine RESTful API and Ant Design to get and put data on UI

OTHER INTERNSHIP

INTERNSHIP OF SUPPORTING ON RUNNING TFT SYSTEM

02/2023 - 05/2023

LOTTE MART HEAD OFFICE - 040 CHANNEL

- Crawling Data from retail competitors (using Nodejs, Puppeteer).
- · Coding marketing mail (Html, CSS, Mailchimp).

SKILLS

- **Programming:** HTML 5, CSS 3, Javascript ES6+, Reactjs 18, Typescript, TailwindCss, Material UI, Redux Thunk, Ant Design, Scss, Styled component, Git, MobX
- · Soft skills: Collaboration, self-taught, problem solve.
- Others: Be able to use English in such as reading documents of any technologies, framework/ library's APIs
- · Languages: English (Intermediate) willing to learn seriously

SALARY EXPECTATION

Expected range is around 12.000.000 VND/month (Net). However, I am open to negotiation and would consider other factors such as benefits, growth opportunities, and the overall compensation package.

KEY STRENGTHS

- · Willing to learn new technologies in Web development.
- Be responsible, and be able to work under high pressure.
- Learn to have the self-discipline to adapt to a new environment and new team.

HONORS & AWARDS

TOEIC 670/990

2021-2022

Bachelor's degree (Classification: Good)

2018 - 2023

DESIRES

- Vision: Become a senior full-stack developer, mastering web applications, within the next 5 years.
- · Network: I aim to build a reputation grounded in honesty and enthusiasm.
- International environment: I'm eager to work in a global company to enhance my English and embrace diverse cultures.

© topcv.vn